http://www.edneyco.com/company/privacy-statement

Getting Cart...
Edney Privacy Statement Data Collection
Edney Distributing Co., Inc. (“Edney”) is committed to protecting the privacy and accuracy of confidential information to the extent possible, subject to provisions of state and federal law. Other than as required by laws that guarantee public access to certain types of information, or in response to subpoenas or other legal instruments that authorize access, personal and confidential information is not actively shared. In particular, we do not re-distribute or sell personal information collected on our web servers.Information collected: Edney servers collect, among other things, the following analytics: Internet Protocol (IP) address of computer being used web pages visited and requestedclickssearch statisticsreferring web pagecity or regionweb page interactionsbrowser used device useddate and timeother demographic information made public and availableEdney does not associate this data to individual user identities.CookiesEdney’s site may use cookies in order to deliver web content specific to individual users' interests or to keep track of online purchasing transactions and other online shopping habits of those visiting our website. Sensitive personal information is not stored within cookies.Web formsEdney uses web forms forms on this site. These forms require users to give contact information [which may include but is not limited to: Name, Company Name, Address, Email, Phone Number, Business contact information, Business Federal Tax ID, Sales Tax Number, Business Officers and Partners, Trade References, Customer Name, Make, Model, and Serial Numbers of Equipment, Service Information for Warranty Claims]. Contact information from the registration form is used only to send material relating to the purpose for which it was collected and will not be sold to another party. Use of collected information:Edney will only use personal information collected from this site for the purpose of communication back to individuals who contact us via the website and for other marketing and communication efforts undertaken by Edney in its sole and absolute discretion.Edney uses browser-IP-address information and anonymous-browser history to report information about site accesses and for profiling purposes. This information is used to improve Web presentation and utilization. IP address information may also be used for troubleshooting purposes.Distribution of collected information:Edney will not disclose, without your consent, personal information collected about you, except for certain circumstances in which disclosure is required by law.Edney will not distribute or sell personal information to third-party organizations.Edney, in its sole and absolute discretion, may use the information for marketing and advertising purposes.
Privacy Statement Revisions:This Privacy Statement was last revised on 2/5/2020. We may change this Privacy Statement at any time and for any reason, without your consent. We encourage you to review this Privacy Statement each time you visit the web site.Responsibility for External Sites:This website may contain links to other web sites. Some of those web sites may be operated by third parties. We provide the links for your convenience, but we do not review, control, or monitor the privacy practices of web sites operated by others, nor do we represent or warrant that the links and websites are safe to visit or secure. We are not responsible for the performance of web sites operated by third parties or for your business dealings with them. Therefore, whenever you leave this web site we recommend that you review each web site's privacy practices and make your own conclusions regarding the adequacy of these practices.How to contact usWhile using this website, you may encounter hypertext links to the Web pages of other organizations not directly affiliated with Edney. Edney does not control the content or information practices of external organizations.
We recommend you review the privacy statements of these organizations.
Edney Distributing Co. Inc., located in the north central United States, is a value added wholesale distributor for equipment manufacturers in North America as well as manufacturers located in countries around the world.
Information
Products
Quickorder
Order Templates
Shopping Cart
My Account
My Account
Favorites
© Copyright 2020 Edney Distributing Co., Inc.
Powered By - Aldrich Web Solutions
